Unarmed and extremely dangerous.
Rapid Fire is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Dwight H. Little.
College student Jake Lo is pursued by smugglers, mobsters and crooked
federal agents after he witnesses a murder by a Mafia kingpin.
Jake Lo, played by Brandon Lee.
Mace Ryan, played by Powers Boothe.
Antonio Serrano, played by Nick Mancuso.
Agent Frank Stewart, played by Raymond J. Barry.
Karla Withers, played by Kate Hodge.
Kinman Tau, played by Tzi Ma.
Rapid Fire is a 1992 American action film directed by Dwight H.
Little and starring Brandon Lee, Powers Boothe and Nick Mancuso.
The film was released in the United States on August 21, 1992.
The film explores themes of martial arts, undercover cop, police
corruption, los angeles, california, drug lord.
The tone is emotional and intense.